publicrecords.directory 2019-05-12

# Public Records Directory

## PRIVACY POLICY

PublicInfo.Directory ("PublicInfo.Directory") is committed to respecting the privacy rights of users of the PublicInfo.Directory website, and the PublicInfo.Directory service, including software applications made available by PublicInfo.Directory, such as the PublicInfo.Directory mobile device application, (together, the "Service"), and to demonstrate its commitment to fair information practices and to the protection of privacy.   
This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Service and not to any websites or services of third parties ("Third-Party Websites"), which may have data collection, storage and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. For additional information, see the section concerning Third-Party Websites, below.   
BY USING THE SERVICE, YOU REPRESENT AND WARRANT THAT YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTOOD, AND AGREE TO THE TERMS OF, THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT UNDERSTAND OR DO NOT AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY CEASE USING OR ACCESSING THE SERVICE.   
Each time You access the Service, the then-current version of this Privacy Policy will apply. Each time You use the Service, we recommend that you check the date of this Privacy Policy (which appears at the end) and review any changes since the last time You used the Service. For additional information, see the section concerning Updates and Changes to Privacy Policy, below.   
**1\. CHILDREN'S PRIVACY** PublicInfo.Directory does not solicit or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If PublicInfo.Directory obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personally identifiable information from a child under the age of 13, PublicInfo.Directory will immediately delete such information from its database. Because PublicInfo.Directory does not collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, PublicInfo.Directory has no such information to use or disclose to third parties. PublicInfo.Directory has designed this Privacy Policy in order to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA"). **2\. INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES** (a) Traffic Data. Like most website and mobile application operators, PublicInfo.Directory automatically gathers information of the sort that browsers automatically make available, including: (i) IP addresses; (ii) domain servers; (iii) types of computers accessing the Service; and (iv) types of Web browsers accessing the Service (collectively "Traffic Data"). Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify You. (b) Cookie Policy - Tracking Over Time and Across Different Websites "Cookies" are text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit or certain emails that you open. A Cookie acts as a string of information stored on a user's computer or mobile device, and that the user's browser provides to the Service each time the user submits a query to the Service. The purpose of a Cookie is to identify the user as a unique user of the Service. PublicInfo.Directory uses two types of Cookies - "first-party cookies" and "third-party cookies." First Party Cookies PublicInfo.Directory uses first-party cookies on the Service, for example the Google Analytics Cookie, for the following purposes: 

  * to gather visitor and access information relevant to customizing the Service to your interests; and 
  * to store your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you use the Service. 
IF YOU DO NOT WISH TO HAVE FIRST-PARTY COOKIES PLACED ON YOUR COMPUTER OR MOBILE DEVICE, YOU SHOULD SET YOUR BROWSERS TO REFUSE COOKIES BEFORE ACCESSING THE SERVICE, WITH THE UNDERSTANDING THAT CERTAIN FEATURES OF THE SERVICE MAY NOT FUNCTION PROPERLY WITHOUT THE AID OF COOKIES. IF YOU REFUSE COOKIES, YOU ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY RESULTING LOSS OF FUNCTIONALITY. Third Party Cookies In addition to these purposes, Google, Inc. ("Google") uses third-party cookies to serve online interest-based advertisements on PublicInfo.Directory. As an important example, Google uses of a cookie known as "DoubleClick" to enable both Google and Google's third party marketing partners to serve advertisements to You based on information gathered during Your use of the Service or Your visit to other websites and services. PublicInfo.Directory may advertise on other third party websites to You after You access the Service. We and third party marketing partners, including without limitation Google, may use first party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) to inform, optimize, and serve advertisements to You based on your use of the Service. Google allows users to customize cookie preferences in Google Ads Settings page. You can also learn more about how to delete or control cookies at www.aboutcookies.org. (c) Ad Serving. PublicInfo.Directory uses third-parties for advertising through the Service and analytics of PublicInfo.Directory users. These third-parties may place cookies on Your computer or mobile device, use web beacons, and gather IP addresses and log data to collect traffic and activity data in order to deliver relevant metrics, content, and advertising. (d) Personally Identifiable Information. In order for You to use certain features of the Service, You will be asked to provide PublicInfo.Directory certain personally identifiable information ("Personal Information"). Personal Information includes the following categories, without limitation: (1) "Contact Data" (such as Your name, phone number, mailing address and e-mail address); (2) "Financial Data" (such as Your credit/debit card number and expiration date); and (3) "Demographic Data" (such as Your zip code). In each case, You will be asked to provide Personal Information; the Service will not gather it surreptitiously. PublicInfo.Directory may supplement the Personal Information You provide with additional Personal Information gathered from public sources or from third-parties (e.g., consumer reporting agencies) who may lawfully provide such information to PublicInfo.Directory. You are under no obligation to provide Personal Information, with the caveat that Your refusal to do so may prevent you from using certain features of the Service. **3\. INFORMATION USE AND DISCLOSURE PRACTICES** (a) Traffic Data and Information Gathered Using Cookies. PublicInfo.Directory analyzes Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies to help PublicInfo.Directory better understand who is using the Service and how they are using it. By identifying patterns and trends in usage, PublicInfo.Directory is able to better design the Service to improve Your experience, and to serve You more relevant and interesting content and advertisements. From time to time, PublicInfo.Directory may release Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Service. PublicInfo.Directory does not attempt to link information gathered using Cookies to Personal Information. (b) Personal Information (i) Generally. PublicInfo.Directory uses Your Contact Data to send You information about PublicInfo.Directory and PublicInfo.Directory's products and services, and to contact You when necessary in connection with the Service. PublicInfo.Directory uses Your Financial Data to verify Your qualifications for certain features of the Service and, when necessary, to bill You. PublicInfo.Directory uses Your Demographic Data to customize and tailor Your experience on the Service. As with Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies, from time to time PublicInfo.Directory may release Demographic Data in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Service. (ii) Disclosure Practices. Except under the following categories of circumstances, PublicInfo.Directory will keep Your Personal Information private, and will not share it with third parties. 
      * Disclosure to Marketing Partners. PublicInfo.Directory may utilize any and all Personal Information to help our clients better understand the demographics of our target audiences as well as to support our marketing data products and services. We may also provide personally identifiable data to partner firms which may include third party marketing companies, affiliates, advertising agencies, and data aggregation companies. Such data may be used by the aforementioned partner firms to provide consumers with information on products and services that may be of interest in accordance with this privacy policy. 
      * Disclosure in Connection with Service. PublicInfo.Directory discloses Personal Information to those who help it provide services, including without limitation those who perform technical, administrative, and data processing tasks such as hosting, billing, fulfillment, and data storage and security. 
      * By Law or to Protect Rights. PublicInfo.Directory discloses Personal Information when required to do so by law, or in response to a subpoena or court order, or when PublicInfo.Directory believes in its sole discretion that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of PublicInfo.Directory, third parties or the public at large. 
      * Business Transfers; Bankruptcy. PublicInfo.Directory reserves the right to transfer all Personal Information in its possession to a successor organization in the event of a merger, acquisition, or bankruptcy or other sale of all or a portion of PublicInfo.Directory's assets. Other than to the extent ordered by a bankruptcy or other court, the use and disclosure of all transferred Personal Information will be subject to this Privacy Policy, or to a new privacy policy if You are given notice of that new privacy policy and an opportunity to affirmatively opt-out of it. Personal Information submitted or collected after a transfer, however, may be subject to a new privacy policy adopted by PublicInfo.Directory's successor organization. 
      * Unpaid Accounts. If You fail to pay any balance owed in consideration of services, PublicInfo.Directory may, as permitted by law, report Your Personal Information, including without limitation Your unpaid balance, to consumer credit reporting services, collection agencies and others. 
**4\. CONSENT TO RECEIVE ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATIONS FROM PUBLICINFO.DIRECTORY** Without limitation, by registering for the Service and/or by providing Your name, email, postal or residential address, and/or phone number through the Service, You hereby expressly consent to receive electronic and other communications from PublicInfo.Directory, over the short term and periodically, including email and short-message service ("SMS" or "text message") communications, regarding the Service, new product offers, promotions, and other matters. You may opt-out of receiving electronic communications at any time by following the unsubscribe instructions contained in each communication; or (b) sending an email to SUPPORT at 123QR dot COM. **5\. CONSENT TO RECEIVE ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATIONS FROM OTHER PUBLICINFO.DIRECTORY USERS** Without limitation, by registering for the Service and/or by providing Your name, email, postal or residential address, and/or phone number through the Service, You hereby consent to receive electronic communications, including email, short-message service ("SMS") messages, instant messages, video conferencing, and other personal messages from other users of the Service. **6\. CONSENT TO RECEIVE ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATIONS FROM PUBLICINFO.DIRECTORY PARTNER MARKETERS** Without limitation, by registering for the Service and/or by providing your name, email, postal or residential address, and/or phone number through the Service, You hereby consent to receive, and openly and knowingly solicit, electronic communications, including email and SMS communications, from PublicInfo.Directory partner firms which may include third party marketing companies, affiliates, advertising agencies, and data aggregation companies regarding their services, including offers, promotions, and other related matters. You may opt-out of receiving electronic communications at any time by (a) following the unsubscribe instructions contained in each communication; or (b) sending an email to SUPPORT at 123QR dot COM. **7\. SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION** PublicInfo.Directory takes security seriously. We utilize commercially reasonable safeguards to protect against the unauthorized access, use, modification, destruction or disclosure of Your Personal Information.. However, due to the realities of data security, PublicInfo.Directory is unable to guarantee that any information provided to us will not be accessed, hacked, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by unauthorized parties. **8\. LOST OR STOLEN INFORMATION** You must promptly notify us if Your credit, bank, other financial institution information, user name or password is lost, stolen or used without permission. In such and event, we will remove that credit card number, bank account information, other financial institution information, user name or password from Your account and updated our records accordingly. **9\. USER ABILITY TO ACCESS, UPDATE, AND CORRECT PERSONAL INFORMATION** PublicInfo.Directory wants Your Personal Information to be complete and accurate. As stated in the Terms of Use, by using the Service, You represent and warrant that all information You provide in connection with Your use of the Service is current, complete, and accurate, and that You will update that information as necessary to maintain its completeness and accuracy. To confirm the completeness and accuracy of, or make changes to, Your Personal Information, send any updates to SUPPORT at 123QR dot COM. **10\. THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES** PublicInfo.Directory neither owns nor controls Third-Party Websites. Accordingly, Third-Party Websites are under no obligation to comply with this Privacy Policy except with respect to Personal Information provided directly to them by PublicInfo.Directory. Before visiting or providing Personal Information to a Third-Party Website, You should inform Yourself of the privacy policies and practices (if any) of that Third-Party Website, and should take those steps necessary to, in Your discretion, protect Your privacy. **11\. PROMOTIONAL ACTIVITIES** From time to time, PublicInfo.Directory may conduct contests, giveaways and other promotions (collectively, "Promotional Activities"). Any information submitted in connection with Promotional Activities will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy. From time to time, PublicInfo.Directory may also ask You to participate in surveys designed to help PublicInfo.Directory improve the Service. Any Personal Information provided to PublicInfo.Directory in connection with any survey will be used only in relation to that survey, and will be disclosed to third parties not bound by this Privacy Policy only in aggregated form. **12\. UPDATES AND CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY** Although most changes are likely to be minor, PublicInfo.Directory reserves the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, update, change or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such update, change or modification on this page. Any such addition, update, change or modification will be effective immediately upon posting. Unless PublicInfo.Directory obtains Your express consent, any revised Privacy Policy will apply only to information collected after the effective date of such revised Privacy Policy, and not to information collected under any earlier Privacy Policy. **13\. BUSINESS TRANSITIONS** In the event PublicInfo.Directory goes through a business transition, including without limitation any merger, acquisition, partnership, business reorganization, debt finance or sale of company assets, or in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership, PublicInfo.Directory may use information collected in accordance with this privacy policy and subject to the restrictions herein, as part of any such business transition. In such instances, your information can be part of the assets transferred. **14\. CALIFORNIA DO-NOT-TRACK DISCLOSURES** Without changing or revoking any of Your privacy protections contained in this privacy policy, it is not feasible at this juncture for PublicInfo.Directory to "respond" to a "do not track" signal as those terms appear in Cal. Bus. & Prof. Code §§ 22575(b)(5). Effective Date: October 1, 2014
